

CONTACT ME AT

- 09959768531
- blk. 26 Lot 17, GK Village,
 Majada In, Canlubang, Calamba
 City, Laguna
- wendellchansuazo11@gmail.com
- https://wendell-suazo.netlify.app/
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/wendell-suazo-8339251aa/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Software Development
- ••• HTML, CSS, SASS, Bootstrap
- •••• Javascript, Jquery, AJAX
- •••• PHP, Laravel, MYSQL, GIT, Github

AWARDS RECEIVED

- President Lister Polytechnic University of the Philippines Oct 2019
- Computer Specialist of the Year Majada In Integrated School
 Mar 2016
- First Honor Majada In Elementary School 2008 - 2010 Grade 4 - Grade 6
- First Honor San Cristobal Elementary School 2005 2007

WENDELL SUAZO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PROFILE SUMMARY

I've been practicing and honing my skills in different programming languages such as javascript, php and mysql. As well as different web frameworks/tools/plugins like laravel, bootstrap, jquery, and SASS. I am trying to dive as deep as I can to these web technologies to use it's full potential.

I am also doing freelance work that helps me earn at the same time learn by experience.

I can do frontend and backend to develop different applications for both professional and personal use.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance Web-Developer

Jan. 2021- present

Create web applications for clients depending on their needs

Backend Developer

IThinkWeb Corporation | July 2021- Jan. 2022

- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Collaborated with other developers

EDUCATION

- Polytechnic University of the Philippines
 Bachelor of Science in Information Technology
 2018 2022
- STI College Calamba
 IT and Mobile App Development, Information Technology
 2016 2018
- Graduated senior high school in STI College Calamba with Technical Vocational strand specializing in IT and Mobile App Development
- Majada In Integrated School 2012 – 2016 Junior High School
- Majada In Elementary School 2008 – 2012 Elementary School
- San Cristobal Elementary School 2004 – 2008 Elementary School